Guide to the Warwick Baker O'Neill Records, 1931-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Account Files, 1973-2001 and undated, (75 boxes)
  - Fruit of the Loom
    - General, 1989-1997, (3 folders) (Box AF31)
    - 1993 Men's Briefs Segmentation Study, 1994 (Box AF31)
    - Advertising examples, 1997, (2 folders) (Box AF31)
    - Agency orientation--Don Siebert visit, 1990 (Box AF31)
    - Brand extension, 1997 (Box AF32)
    - Brand review, 1991 (Box AF32)
    - Business review, 1996, (2 folders) (Box AF32)
    - Campaign planning, 1996 (Box AF32)
    - Comfort concepts, 1996 (Box AF32)
    - Consumer Purchases of Men's and Boys' Underwear, 1996 (Box AF32)
    - Creative, 1992-1993 (Box AF32)
    - Creative/Media/Research, 1997 (Box AF32)
    - Creative strategy, 1997 (Box AF32)
    - Daywear focus groups, 1990 (Box AF32)
    - Focus groups, 1997 (Box AF32)
    - Long term vision--Competitive websites, 1997 (Box AF32)
    - Market analysis, 1996 (Box AF33)
    - Men's underwear study, 1996-1997 (Box AF33)
    - Packaging research, 1996 (Box AF33)
    - Planning work session, 1990 (Box AF33)
    - Portfolio strategy for the apparel category, 1997 (Box AF33)
    - Positioning development, 1993 (Box AF33)
    - Presentation, 1997 (Box AF33)
    - Research, 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box AF33)
    - Sales meeting, 1989 (Box AF33)
    - Strategy development, 1996 (Box AF33)
    - Umbrella positioning project, 1993 (Box AF33)
    - Website proposal, 1997 (Box AF33)
    - Client meeting, 1991-1992 (Box AF34)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box AF34)
    - Country Comfort tour, 1997 (Box AF34)
    - Creative, 1997 (Box AF34)
    - Loosen Your Collar concerts, 1997 (Box AF34)
    - Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box AF34)
    - Presentation, 1997, (3 folders) (Box AF34)
    - Pro Player, 1996, (2 folders) (Box AF34)
    - Research, 1989-1997, (2 folders) (Box AF35)
    - Review, 1994-1995 (Box AF35)
  - Gleneagles
    - General, 1997 (Box AF35)
  - Heineken Group
    - General Files
      - Budget, 1995 (Box AF35)
      - Competitive beer spending, 1994 (Box AF35)
      - Fascinating Art programs, 1994 (Box AF35)
      - Radio--ESPN Radio Network, 1995 (Box AF35)
      - Radio--Westwood One Radio Network, 1994-1995 (Box AF35)
      - Research, 1993, (2 folders) (Box AF36)
      - Research--Censydiam report, undated (Box AF36)
      - U.S. beer market, 1994, (2 folders) (Box AF36)
      - Vincent Printing (VPI) outdoor poster production, undated (Box AF36)
      - Account planning, 1995-1996 (Box Amstel Light)
      - Attitude and usage studies, 1995 (Box Amstel Light)
      - Awareness studies, 1995 (Box Amstel Light)
      - Billboard and radio tests, 1995-1996, (3 folders) (Box AF37)
      - Brand review, 1985-1988 (Box AF37)
      - Budget, 1994 (Box AF37)
      - Campaign results, 1995 (Box AF37)
      - Celebrities, 1988-1992 (Box AF37)
      - Claim substantiation, 1994 (Box AF37)
      - College football, 1993 (Box AF37)
      - Complaints, 1993 (Box AF37)
      - Copy tests, 1994-1996, (1-3 of 4 folders) (Box AF37)
      - Copy tests, 1994-1996, (4 of 4 folders) (Box AF38)
      - Creative (Box AF38)
      - General, 1994-1995 (Box AF38)
      - Briefing, 1995 (Box AF38)
      - Development, 1995 (Box AF38)
      - Research, 1994 (Box AF38)
      - Strategy, 1994 (Box AF38)
      - Timetable, 1994 (Box AF38)
      - Demographics/Psychographics, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box AF38)
      - Flowcharts, 1993 (Box AF38)
      - Focus groups, 1994 (Box AF38)
      - General, 1984-1998 (Box AF38)
      - Generation X presentation, undated (Box AF38)
      - Label test, 1995 (Box AF39)
      - Market segmentation, 1996 (Box AF39)
      - Marketing brief, 1994 (Box AF39)
      - Media (Box AF39)
      - General, 1994-1995, (3 folders) (Box AF39)
      - Plan, 1992 (Box AF39)
      - Planning, 1994-1995, (1-3 of 6 folders) (Box AF39)
      - Planning, 1994-1995, (4-6 of 6 folders) (Box AF40)
      - Omnibus study, 1995 (Box AF40)
      - Packaging, 1994 (Box AF40)
      - Point of sale, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box AF40)
      - Positioning, 1994, (2 folders) (Box AF40)
      - Print and outdoor, 1995 (Box AF40)
      - Print creative, 1994 (Box AF40)
      - Print rotation, 1994 (Box AF40)
      - Psychographics, 1995 (Box AF40)
      - Qualitative, 1992 (Box AF40)
      - Radio, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box AF41)
      - Radio tests, 1995, (2 folders) (Box AF41)
      - Recall, undated (Box AF41)
      - Research, 1994-1996, (7 folders) (Box AF41)
      - Research proposal, 1988 (Box AF41)
      - Right campaign, 1992 (Box AF41)
      - Sales data, 1993-1994 (Box AF42)
      - Scripts, 1984-1987 (Box AF42)
      - Seasonality, 1994 (Box AF42)
      - Steve Davis review, 1995 (Box AF42)
      - Storyboard--Amstel Light-Right campaign, undated (Box AF42)
      - Strategy, 1988-1994, (6 folders) (Box AF42)
      - Talent, 1995 (Box AF42)
      - Television, 1988-1995, (2 folders) (Box AF42)
      - Three-year plan, 1995 (Box AF42)
      - Tracking, 1992-1996, (1-7 of 9 folders) (Box AF43)
      - Tracking, 1992-1996, (8-9 of 9 folders) (Box AF44)
    - Heineken
      - Advertising development, 1988 (Box AF44)
      - Advertising study, 1990 (Box AF44)
      - Agency point of view, undated (Box AF44)
      - Authorizations, 1995 (Box AF44)
      - Awareness and usage questionnaire, 1992 (Box AF44)
      - Beer consumption, 1988 (Box AF44)
      - Brand Penetration Index (BPI), 1992 and undated (Box AF44)
      - Budget reports, 1994-1995, (3 folders) (Box AF44)
      - Communications plan, 1994 (Box AF44)
      - Competitive, 1988 (Box AF44)
      - Copy research, 1988 (Box AF45)
      - Copy test--Best Friends campaign, 1995 (Box AF45)
      - Credit/Make-good reports, 1995 (Box AF45)
      - Distributor video, 1995 (Box AF45)
      - Estimates, 1994, (2 folders) (Box AF45)
      - Ethnic/Hispanic markets, 1994 (Box AF45)
      - Flowcharts, 1993 (Box AF45)
      - Focus groups, 1988 (Box AF45)
      - Gallup study of U.S. imported beer market, 1995 (Box AF45)
      - General, 1988 (Box AF45)
      - Grizzly strategy, 1988 (Box AF45)
      - Hispanic commercial, 1988 (Box AF45)
      - Key Facts book, 1995 (Box AF45)
      - Media, 1988-1995, (1-2 of 9 folders) (Box AF45)
      - Media, 1988-1995, (3-9 of 9 folders) (Box AF46)
      - Past 30 days drinkers, 1993 (Box AF47)
      - Positioning, 1995 (Box AF47)
      - Qualitative bottle/label study, 1988 (Box AF47)
      - Qualitative research, 1987-1994, (2 folders) (Box AF47)
      - Quotes from one-on-ones, 1988 (Box AF47)
      - Radio--Hispanic, 1995 (Box AF47)
      - Radio scripts, 1988 (Box AF47)
      - Research, 1988-1995 and undated, (6 folders) (Box AF47)
      - Research proposal, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box AF47)
      - Slim project, 1992 (Box AF48)
      - Strategy, 1995 (Box AF48)
      - Television, 1988 (Box AF48)
      - Topline usage and awareness, 1988 (Box AF48)
      - Tracking, 1994-1996, (6 folders) (Box AF48)
      - Trade print, 1995 (Box AF48)
      - Usage and attitude, 1994 (Box AF48)
    - Van Munching & Co.
      - Advertising manual, 1991 (Box AF49)
      - Broadcast traffic, 1995 (Box AF49)
      - Buckler positioning, 1992 (Box AF49)
      - Buckler strategy, 1989-1994 (Box AF49)
      - Budget reports, 1993 (Box AF49)
      - Coverage of IRI markets, 1993 (Box AF49)
      - Distributor video, 1990-1994, (4 folders) (Box AF49)
      - Estimates, 1994, (1 of 5 folders) (Box AF49)
      - Estimates, 1994, (2-5 of 5 folders) (Box AF50)
      - Field trips, 1988 (Box AF50)
      - General, 1990-1991 (Box AF50)
      - Hispanic copy, 1994 (Box AF50)
      - Market by market analysis, 1994 (Box AF50)
      - Media, 1993-1995, (1 of 13 folders) (Box AF50)
      - Media, 1993-1995, (2-7 of 13 folders) (Box AF51)
      - Media, 1993-1995, (8-13 of 13 folders) (Box AF52)
      - Media opportunities, 1993 (Box AF52)
      - Media planning, 1993-1994, (4 folders) (Box AF53)
      - Merchandising, undated (Box AF53)
      - Opportunities meeting, 1991 (Box AF53)
      - Positioning, 1992 (Box AF53)
      - Print rotation, 1994 (Box AF53)
      - Research, 1990-1992 (Box AF53)
      - Santa Maria, 1994 (Box AF53)
      - Strategy, 1994 (Box AF53)
      - Tarwebok, 1994 (Box AF54)
      - Television sports, 1993-1994 (Box AF54)
      - Time agreement, 1993-1994 (Box AF54)
      - Trade advertising, 1993 (Box AF54)
      - Trade media, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box AF54)
      - World Cup of Golf, 1993, (3 folders) (Box AF54)
  - IAMS
    - General, 1992-1993 (Box AF55)
    - Consumer loyalty, 1992 (Box AF55)
    - Eukanuba--Puppy Print newsletter, 1993 (Box AF55)
  - Knorr
    - Creative strategy, 1991-1997, (2 folders) (Box AF55)
    - Golden Rules, 1996 (Box AF55)
  - Lehn & Fink
    - General, 1989-1992 (Box AF55)
    - Lysol, 1992-1994, (1-2 of 5 folders) (Box AF55)
    - Lysol, 1992-1994, (3-5 of 5 folders) (Box AF56)
    - Resolve carpet cleaner, 1991-1997 (Box AF56)
  - MFS Asset Management
    - Articles on mutual fund market, 1992 and undated (Box AF56)
    - Distribution channels for mutual funds, 1994 (Box AF56)
    - Profiles of first-time mutual fund buyers, 1994 (Box AF56)
    - Research, 1996 (Box AF56)
  - Modern Healthcare Daily
    - Printed material, 1998 (Box AF56)
  - Panasonic
    - Massage lounger, 1996 (Box AF57)
    - Men's shaver, 1995-1997 (Box AF57)
    - Smooth Operator razor, 1992 (Box AF57)
  - Parade Magazine
    - General, 1996 (Box AF57)
    - Recency presentation, undated (Box AF57)
  - Pat Doran Sportscast
    - Super show, 1995 (Box AF57)
  - Prodigy
    - General, 1996-1997, (1-4 of 6 folders) (Box AF57)
    - General, 1996-1997, (5-6 of 6 folders) (Box AF58)
    - Agency credentials, undated (Box AF58)
    - Articles, 1997 (Box AF58)
    - Compensation plan, 1997 (Box AF58)
    - Competitive, 1996-1997 (Box AF58)
    - Internet, 1997 (Box AF58)
    - ISP articles, 1996 (Box AF58)
    - Program Fact Book, 1997, (2 folders) (Box AF58)
    - Public relations strategy, 1996-1997 (Box AF59)
  - Prudential Insurance
    - Case history, undated (Box AF59)
  - Reckitt & Colman
    - All-purpose cleaner study, 1996 (Box AF59)
    - Articles on condiments, 1995-1996 (Box AF59)
    - Carpet and upholstery cleaning, 1993 (Box AF59)
    - Easy-Off oven cleaner, 1996 (Box AF59)
    - French's French-Fried Onions, 1997 (Box AF59)
    - Hard surface cleaners, 1996 (Box AF59)
    - Hard surface market study, 1996 (Box AF59)
    - Oven cleaners, 1996 (Box AF59)
    - Resolve carpet cleaner, 1997 (Box AF59)
    - Rid-X, 1996-1997, (1 of 3 folders) (Box AF59)
    - Rid-X, 1996-1997, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box AF60)
    - Rug cleaner study, 1991, (4 folders) (Box AF60)
  - Rocco
    - Shady Brook Farms scripts, 1986-1987 (Box AF60)
  - Schering-Plough
    - Lotrimin, 1996 (Box AF60)
    - Personal care ingredient naming, 1997 (Box AF60)
  - Seagram
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box AF60)
    - General, 1974-1980s (Box AF60)
  - Selfcare Consumer Products Inc. (SCPI)
    - General, 1997 (Box AF61)
  - SNET
    - General, 1996, (2 folders) (Box AF61)
    - Branding/Positioning, 1996 (Box AF61)
    - Presentation, circa 1996 (Box AF61)
  - Tennis Industry Association
    - General, 1995 (Box AF61)
    - Image campaign, 1996 (Box AF61)
    - Mall tennis program, 1995 (Box AF61)
    - Presentation, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box AF61)
    - Tracking, 1996 (Box AF61)
  - Timex
    - All Star Swing Festival, 1973, (2 folders) (Box AF62)
  - Trudy Toys
    - Catalog, 1984 (Box AF62)
  - U.S. Tobacco
    - General, 1983-1987 (Box AF62)
    - Annual golf outing, 1987-1991 (Box AF62)
    - Annual reports, 1980-1986 (Box AF62)
    - FTC on smokeless tobacco, 1984-1985 (Box AF62)
    - Generation X, 1995 (Box AF62)
    - Global branding, undated (Box AF62)
    - House of Windsor scripts (Red Skelton), 1977-1978 (Box AF62)
    - Skoal, 1996 (Box AF62)
  - Weight Watchers
    - Qualitative study, 1996 (Box AF63)
  - West Point Pepperell
    - Accessories research, 1990 (Box AF63)
    - Bed/Bath market data, 1985-1988, (2 folders) (Box AF63)
    - Creative presentation, 1989 (Box AF63)
    - Home furnishings study, 1989 (Box AF63)
    - Lady Pepperell/Martex, 1989 (Box AF63)
    - Meetings, 1989 (Box AF63)
    - Research, 1989, (2 folders) (Box AF63)
    - Sales force presentation, 1989 (Box AF63)
    - Sheets and towels tracking study, 1989 (Box AF63)
    - Slides, 1989 (Box AF64)
    - Strategy, 1989 (Box AF64)
  - Western Publishing
    - General, 1992-1994 (Box AF64)
    - Annual reports, 1993 (Box AF64)
    - Client correspondence, 1994 (Box AF64)
    - Songburst (country and western game), 1992 (Box AF64)
    - Special projects, 1994 (Box AF64)
  - Script collection
    - Ad Council
      - See the Sickness, 1986 (Box AF65)
    - Benjamin Moore
      - $2.00 Off, 1975 (Box AF65)
      - 5 Second Closing, 1976 (Box AF65)
      - Architect, 1978-1984 (Box AF65)
      - Ball Game, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Banking, 1976-1977 (Box AF65)
      - Big Sale, undated (Box AF65)
      - Billboard, 1980 (Box AF65)
      - Busy Man, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Childproof, 1976 (Box AF65)
      - Dealer Sales, undated (Box AF65)
      - Decorator's Delight, undated (Box AF65)
      - Doctor, 1980 (Box AF65)
      - Do It Yourselfer, 1979-1984 (Box AF65)
      - Double Combo, 1978 (Box AF65)
      - Doug Shephard, 1983 (Box AF65)
      - Frustrated Man, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - George Pappas, 1983-1985 (Box AF65)
      - Good, Better, 1975-1979 (Box AF65)
      - Harriet Muranko, 1983-1984 (Box AF65)
      - Julie Scherer, 1983-1985 (Box AF65)
      - Latex Only, 1978 (Box AF65)
      - Lighthouse, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Lighthouse Keeper, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Messy Kid, 1980-1982 (Box AF65)
      - Moorglo, Moorgard, Moor White, 1984 (Box AF65)
      - Moorglo Sale, 1984 (Box AF65)
      - Moorwood Stains, 1983 (Box AF65)
      - Moving House, 1979 (Box AF65)
      - Newlyweds, 1973-1975 (Box AF65)
      - Opening and closing billboard, 1973 (Box AF65)
      - Paint Farm, 1988 (Box AF65)
      - Painter, 1973 (Box AF65)
      - Prospector, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Real People, 1983 (Box AF65)
      - Reasons, 1975-1977 (Box AF65)
      - Regal Wall Satin, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Rick Swiger, 1983-1985 (Box AF65)
      - Skip Miller, 1983 (Box AF65)
      - Special Offer, undated (Box AF65)
      - Spokesman--Natural Beauty, undated (Box AF65)
      - Stacking, 1976-1977 (Box AF65)
      - Stain, 1978 (Box AF65)
      - Stevens/New Home, 1986 (Box AF65)
      - The Game, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Triple Combo, 1978 (Box AF65)
      - Weatherman, undated (Box AF65)
      - Well-Protected, undated (Box AF65)
      - Who Told You That?, 1977 (Box AF65)
    - Burlington
      - Apparel, 1982 (Box AF65)
      - Bioguard Socks, 1979 (Box AF65)
      - Caress Sheets Dracula, 1979 (Box AF65)
      - Change into Colorful Corduroy, 1984 (Box AF65)
      - Crossfire Corduroy Fashion Ave., 1983 (Box AF65)
      - Domestics, 1982 (Box AF65)
      - Don't Look Now, undated (Box AF65)
      - Fashion Avenue, 1983 (Box AF65)
      - Furniture/Trees, 1979 (Box AF65)
      - Hosiery/Socks, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Hug Bunny--A Little Bit of Bunny, 1979 (Box AF65)
      - Interrupted Weave, undated (Box AF65)
      - Jeans Plus, 1984 (Box AF65)
      - Klopman--Sew Easy, 1978 (Box AF65)
      - Laura Ashley bedliners--My World, 1985 (Box AF65)
      - Lees Carpets--Doors, 1986 (Box AF65)
      - Sewing/Furniture, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Sheets/Rugs, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - Silky Woven--Born to be Beautiful, 1984 (Box AF65)
      - So Soft So Sheer pantyhose, undated (Box AF65)
    - BVD
      - In My BVDs, 1987-1988 (Box AF65)
    - Coty-Pfizer (Box AF65)
    - Emeraude
      - Emeraude of Your Life, 1981 (Box AF65)
      - Gift-Givers, 1982 (Box AF65)
      - Give Someone Love, 1982 (Box AF65)
      - He Loves Me, 1983 (Box AF65)
      - One Man/One Fragrance, 1984-1985 (Box AF65)
      - Someone Special, 1983 (Box AF65)
    - Stetson
      - Day, 1983-1984 (Box AF65)
      - Easy for You, 1985 (Box AF65)
      - Fitter, undated (Box AF65)
      - Fits, 1981 (Box AF65)
    - CPC/Ho Cereal
      - Bundle Up, 1981 (Box AF65)
      - Goldilocks, 1977 (Box AF65)
      - No Contest, 1984 (Box AF65)
      - We Want Ho, 1983 (Box AF65)
    - Crafted with Pride
      - Department Store, 1988 (Box AF65)
      - Miss America Pageant, 1988 (Box AF65)
      - Quick Change, 1988 (Box AF66)
      - Tell All the World, 1987 (Box AF66)
    - Crosslands Savings, 1988 (Box AF66)
    - D-Con
      - D-Stroy One Day Later, 1988 (Box AF66)
      - Exact, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Flea and Tick, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Flea Kill/Egg Nightmare, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Four Gone, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Lure 'n Kill, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Mouse Killing Station, 1987 (Box AF66)
      - Resolve, 1986-1988 (Box AF66)
      - Rodenticide, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Split :30s, 1985-1986 (Box AF66)
    - Economics Lab
      - Scrub Free, 1983 (Box AF66)
    - Food from Britain, 1984 (Box AF66)
    - Glenbrook Labs
      - Calcitrel, 1985-1986 (Box AF66)
      - Fresh Again, 1983 (Box AF66)
      - Maximum Strength Midol, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Midol 200, 1987-1988 (Box AF66)
      - Midol PMS, 1985-1987 (Box AF66)
    - Glenbrook/Lehn & Fink--Stri-Dex
      - 8 Hours, 1976-1977 (Box AF66)
      - Academic, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Anti-Drug, 1988 (Box AF66)
      - Audition, undated (Box AF66)
      - Boing, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Bye-Bye, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Coach, 1980 (Box AF66)
      - Come on Over to My Pad, 1977-1980 (Box AF66)
      - Country Singer, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Custer, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Everywhere, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Finiculi Finicula, 1980 (Box AF66)
      - Freddie, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Girlfriends, 1979 (Box AF66)
      - Groupies, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Hey Little Lady, 1978 (Box AF66)
      - I Like a Liquid, 1976 (Box AF66)
      - Juke Box, 1984 (Box AF66)
      - Keeps Working, 1976 (Box AF66)
      - Let's Take a Test, 1981 (Box AF66)
      - Live DJ Stephanie, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Look Your Best, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Lookout Louie, undated (Box AF66)
      - Medicinal, undated (Box AF66)
      - Mother and Daughter, 1977 (Box AF66)
      - My Pad, 1977 (Box AF66)
      - Name the Time, 1978 (Box AF66)
      - Oath, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Older Brother, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Put Your Face to the Test, 1981 (Box AF66)
      - Romeo and Juliet, 1980 (Box AF66)
      - See Medicine, 1977 (Box AF66)
      - See Proof, 1977 (Box AF66)
      - Singer, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Skateboard, 1977 (Box AF66)
      - Soaps, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Stone Age, 1986 (Box AF66)
      - Take That, Pimples, 1977 (Box AF66)
      - Talk Show, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - The Prize Is on the Pad, 1983 (Box AF66)
      - The Proof Is on the Pad, 1981 (Box AF66)
      - The Wizard, 1980 (Box AF66)
      - Treat Yourself Beautifully, undated (Box AF66)
      - Voice, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Wipeout, 1987 (Box AF66)
    - Grolsch--Six Pack/Art from Holland, 1981 (Box AF66)
    - J. Victori Wines--Calvin Coolers, 1986 (Box AF66)
    - Knorr, 1987-1988 (Box AF66)
    - Lehn & Fink
      - Glass-Mates, 1985 (Box AF66)
      - Medi-Quik, 1976 (Box AF66)
      - Miami Project/Marc Buoniconti Fund, 1987 (Box AF66)
    - Rocco/Shadybrook Farms Turkeys, 1987 (Box AF66)
    - U.S. Tobacco Co.
      - Beach, 1980 (Box AF67)
      - Borkum Riff--Brul, 1983 (Box AF67)
      - Charlie Daniels, 1981-1982 (Box AF67)
      - Copenhagen--Babco, 1985 (Box AF67)
      - Copenhagen--Cale Yarbrough, 1982-1983 (Box AF67)
      - Happy Days--Shep Messing, 1980 (Box AF67)
      - House of Windsor--Red Skelton, 1977-1978 (Box AF67)
      - House of Windsor--Store, 1980 (Box AF67)
      - Miscellaneous scripts, 1971-1985 (Box AF67)
      - Moist
        - Bobby Mercer, undated (Box AF67)
        - Cale Yarbrough, 1982 (Box AF67)
        - Carlton Fisk, 1978 (Box AF67)
        - Charlie Daniels, 1984 (Box AF67)
        - Earl Campbell, 1979-1981 (Box AF67)
        - Harry Gant, 1983 (Box AF67)
        - Shep Messing, 1978 (Box AF67)
        - Smokeless, undated (Box AF67)
        - Steve Towle, undated (Box AF67)
        - Tackling, 1978 (Box AF67)
        - Walt Garrison, 1977-1983 (Box AF67)
      - Skoal
        - Bobby Mercer, 1979-1983 (Box AF67)
        - Charlie Daniels, 1980-1985 (Box AF67)
        - Harry Gant, 1982-1983 (Box AF67)
        - Walt Garrison, 1978-1982 (Box AF67)
      - Skoal Bandits
        - Airplane, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Astute Leaders, 1983 (Box AF67)
        - Basketball, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Bruce Bowman, 1984 (Box AF67)
        - Checkered Flag, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Double Bonus, 1984 (Box AF67)
        - Factory, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Four Wheel, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Friend, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Harry Gant, 1981-1984 (Box AF67)
        - Kent Weld, 1984 (Box AF67)
        - Little Pouch, 1983 (Box AF67)
        - Minty Flavor, 1984 (Box AF67)
        - Movies, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Pouch, 1983 (Box AF67)
        - Saturday Night, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Take Out, 1985-1986 (Box AF67)
        - Team Pleasure, undated (Box AF67)
        - TV billboard, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Skoal/Happy Days--Nick Buoniconti, 1978 (Box AF67)
      - Skoal Long Cut
        - America Loves with Bob Sheppard, 1983 (Box AF67)
        - Asphalt, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Bad Guitar, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Basketball, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Coal Mine, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Daily News, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Farm, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Fishing Forecast, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Is What He Wants to Be, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Let Me Tell You, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Log Rolling, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Long Long Haul, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Minty Flavor, 1984 (Box AF67)
        - Pinch Hitter, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Rodeo, 1986 (Box AF67)
        - Sports Arena, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Summer 500 Free, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Trucker's Radio, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - TV billboard, 1985 (Box AF67)
        - Walt Garrison, 1984-1985 (Box AF67)
        - Walt Garrison miscellaneous, 1975-1982 (Box AF67)
        - Weyman and Bruton, 1982 (Box AF67)
    - Van Munching
      - Grizzly Beer--Jerry Seinfeld, 1988 (Box AF67)
      - Heineken, 1988 (Box AF67)
    - Winthrop
      - Campho-Phenique, 1985-1988 (Box AF67)
  - Restricted Files
    - Bacardi
      - Bacardi Light creative, 1999 (Box AF-R1)
      - Brand Essence Manual, 1999 (Box AF-R1)
      - General, 1992-1999, (4 folders) (Box AF-R1)
      - Just Add Bacardi/Bacardi by Night, 1994-1999 (Box AF-R1)
      - Presentations, 1999, (2 folders) (Box AF-R2)
      - Strategy, 1999 (Box AF-R2)
    - Bausch & Lomb
      - Moisture Eyes, 1998, (2 folders) (Box AF-R2)
      - Research, 1998 (Box AF-R2)
      - Topline reports, 1996-1998 (Box AF-R2)
    - Best Foods
      - Knorr, 1998, (2 folders) (Box AF-R3)
    - East Coast Energy Council (ECEC)
      - Brusking Goldring report on energy deregulation, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
      - Exploratory study, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
      - Key research learning, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
    - Fruit of the Loom
      - Brand strategy, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
      - BVD, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
      - Gitano sales meeting, 1999 (Box AF-R3)
      - Reports, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
      - Research, 1998-1999 (Box AF-R3)
      - Sales meeting, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
      - Winning at Retail, 1999 (Box AF-R3)
    - GridNet
      - General, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
      - Competitive, 1998 (Box AF-R3)
    - Harper Collins
      - General, 1998 (Box AF-R4)
    - Lexmark
      - Advertising awareness, 1999 (Box AF-R4)
      - Brand awareness, 2000 (Box AF-R4)
      - Color laser printer, circa 2000 (Box AF-R4)
      - Color printing, 2000 (Box AF-R4)
      - Competitive, 2000, (4 folders) (Box AF-R4)